Narrator: Hi I'm Neil. Thanks for joining me on English at Work - [[a new series (全新系列)]] of programmes set in an office, full of top tips to help you learn some useful business language  which you could use in the workplace.
In the next few minutes you can join me on an introductory tour around one of London's biggest imitation plastic fruit manufacturers, called Tip Top Trading.
We're going to hear from some of the employees  that work so hard to keep the business running smoothly.
So come on then! Let's step into the office and [[eavesdrop(偷聽)]] on Tip Top Trading's possible newest recruit. I say 'possible' because she is still being interviewed for the job of Sales Executive
Anna: Firstly, this job is an ideal match for my skills and experience:  I've spent several years working in sales and [I get on with people easily(我很好相處)].
Well, I mean, apart from the ones I don't like of course!
Secondly, I know Tip Top Trading is one of the fastest-growing companies in London, and I want to be part of that.
Paul: That's absolutely right. Tip Top Trading is the fastest-growing company in the plastic fruits sector.
Narrator: [[ Well said(說得好) ]], Anna! If she gets that job I'm sure she'll be an asset to the company.
The decision is in the hands of Manager, Paul, who we heard there. He's a nice guy really,
a little [[disorganised(雜亂無章)]], but when things go wrong he's got to take charge a bit like this
Paul: Yesterday was not a great day. Two clients came in with serious
complaints. Mrs Kumquat received a delivery of imitation bananas that were purple - [[not very convincing(不太有說服力)]], and Mr Lime ordered grapefruits, but got pineapples. Tom!
Tom: Yeah, listen...
Paul: Were you responsible for these errors?
Tom: Well... yes, but -
Paul: Look, mistakes happen. But it seems that Mrs Kumquat left our offices even angrier than  when she came in and she says she will never use Tip, Top Trading again!
Tom: I tried my best.
Paul: Hmmm.
Narrator: Ah yes, Tom! I hadn't warned you about Tom, one of the company's top Sales Executives - he's good...
Tom: (on phone) Tom speaking. Yah! Frankie! So what's the latest, are we on?
... but his interpersonal skills need working on. Listen to this!
Tom:[[ My computer has crashed(我電腦當機了) ]]. I've lost my phone. And there's a big, BIG problem with my timetable. I have two meetings scheduled at the same time with two extremely important clients. I can't do them both at once!
See what I mean! Now, every office needs a good office assistant - and Tip Top Trading is no exception. It's got Denise, who's there to assist, organise and sometimes make the tea...
Denise: Oh sorry excuse me, here's your tea, Paul.
Paul: Thanks Denise.
Narrator: But goodness! She likes to talk...
Denise: Really! 'Denise do this! Denise do that!' I'm telling you Sharon, I've almost had enough! [[I get treated like I'm some kind of servant!(我被當佣人對待)]]
Narrator: That's Denise! I think we'll just leave the office now and let them get on with their work
So that's Tip Top Trading. There are plenty of other people we'll meet along the way...
so go on, why don't you join me for English at Work from bbclearningenglish.com. See ya!